很久以前 阿肯人统治整个银河系
它们身后满是恐怖和疮痍
它们那可怕的力量之源
遗落在乌诺波里斯星球的密室中
其中蕴含着神秘的永生之泉
密室只能被一把独一无二的钥匙打开
一旦被人找到
它将会引导发现者得到永生之泉
然而 那把钥匙令所有接触到它的人变得疯狂
阿肯人最终被击败 他们的力量之源被锁在密室中的时候
那把钥匙也被流放到宇宙深处
再也没有出现过
直到现在
哼 快点投降 你这混蛋
可恶 又来了
我已经等不及拿到那些新设备了
我已经受够了这些便宜货了
泰勒 我好像发现了什么
什么东西?
我也不知道
小心点 这可能是四级生化物品
这到底是什么?
它在做什么?
真是诡异
怎么回事?你还好吧？
需要我呼叫紧急救助吗?
不 不要 求求你
你在干什么
守护者已经显灵
钥匙已经被发现了
奥丁 告诉我们
巨大的黑暗是否即将到来?
是的 正如古书说记载的那样
黑暗即将回归
邪恶即将到来
我们必须做好准备守护密室
桑达斯  3号区域
我们还在等待当地核心的初步分析结果
什么？他们下去多久了？
超过12个小时 他们肯定快疯了
真奇怪  系统没问他 但一直没有回复  怪事
送几个人下去 我要弄清楚到底发生什么事情
我需要一艘大船去些地方
见鬼 你知道你在做什么吗
保安 到舰桥来
还有其他蠢问题吗?
胖子  你的名字和职务
- 兰伯特 长官  导航员
- 开船
吉尔曼 St  吉尔曼
若我想知道你的名字  呆瓜 我会问你的
接管引擎
导航定位至 BR-549 区域7
另外 来人把这些垃圾弄走
另外
你有20秒时间带我们离开这里
Hi
你还在这里干啥?
我知道  我一会就会上学迟到
爸爸在哪儿?
他在议会 我以为你也应该去的
哦 糟糕
你相信那些所谓的不朽的妄言吗?
想想看 一把愚蠢的钥匙?
他是个骗子 瞧着吧
听我说 这家伙自从那天开始就变得越来越诡异了
想想看再来10年? 见鬼  甚至100年
你说到点子上了
我讨厌这鬼地方 特别是翻遍这个丑陋的地方
I am getting sick of it Going all over the bloody place
寻找一个荒谬的谎言
Looking for a stupid compound
-你找到了什么东西？-一个FAKK2号行星
- What have you got?  - A FAKK 2 planet  sir
嗯 这地方对碳基生命来说意味着死亡
Death to all carbon based life forms
议会指定的二级杀戮死亡地带
Federation Assigned Kitogenic Killzone to the second level
这里是一个死行星
Which means it's a dead planet
对它进行扫描
Scan it anyway
我不明白
I don't get it
这外面有生命存在
There's life out there
这个FAKK2号行星的注册信息肯定过时了
The FAKK 2 must have been from an old registry
我想要这个地方H2O-471化合物的生物扫描结果
I want a bio-scan for compound H2O-471
他们的生态系统里一定有什么线索
There are small traces in their systems
到处都有不朽的线索
Yeah  Immortality all over the place
你
You
记着你的小命还不是不朽的
Just remember you're not immortal yet
这地方叫什么？
What's this place called?
伊甸 长官
Eden  sir
欢迎来到天堂
Welcome to paradise
我们的灌溉计划已经初见成效
And our irrigation program is already showing promise
上半年农产品的产量增长了5个百分点
Agro-production is up five percent in the last six months
我们的扩张项目也将进入第二阶段
Phase two of our expansion project
诺玛区的开发 按照程序将在三周后开始
the development of the Noma Valley will begin in three weeks as scheduled
一切都很顺利 先生门女士们 我们的未来一片光明
Things look good  ladies and gentlemen Our future is bright
-你去帮助凯瑞 我去打开防卫系统。
- Help Kerrie  I'll get our air defences up
快 这边走
Quickly  This way
凯瑞
Kerrie
朱莉
Julie
父亲
Father
看来我们的家伙有点好战
Looks like the boys got a little trigger-happy
在做煎蛋卷时 先得打碎几个鸡蛋
When making an omelette one breaks a few eggs
这 我来帮你
Here  let me help you
他们在攻击
They attacked
-你还好吗？-我们没希望了
- You okay? - We never had a chance
嘿 看看这个 一个女人
Hey  look at this  A live one
离她远点
Leave her alone
滚开 离我远点
Get off of me  Let me go
活泼又性感
Feisty and sexy
伙计们小心点 这家伙是战利品
Careful boys  this one's a keeper
-把他们铐起来 -是 长官
- Pack 'em up - Yes  sir
快点 伙计们 我们要离开了
Splitsville  boys  We're moving out
等等我
Wait for me
可怜的小家伙 你只能靠你自己了
Lover-boy  you're on your own
你不能就这样扔下我
You can't just leave me here like this
等会
Wait a minute  man
就像他说的 这是个死行星
Like the sign says  a dead planet
这不会伤到你 只是一个DNA测试
This won't hurt  It's just a DNA test
好结果总是来得晚
The good stuff comes later
博士 从其他人开始
Start with the others  Doc
-这个人非常独特  -当然
- This one's special - But of course
我需要的东西就在你们体内
What I need is in your system
虽然不足以另你们不朽
Not enough to make you immortal
但是足以令你们保持美丽和健康 特别是你
but it probably keeps your people beautiful and healthy  Especially you
我会把你留到最后
I'll save you for last
假如你运气好的话 亲爱的 最好放聪明一点
And if you're lucky  my dear and play your cards right
我们会待在一起很长时间
we'll spend a lot of quality time together
完美 我知道你不会令我失望的
Perfect  I knew you wouldn't disappoint me
把她清理干净
Clean her up
相信不用我强调
And I don't have to remind your kind
她是我的
she's mine
我应该成为一个厨师的
I should have been a cook
尝尝这个
Try this for an appetiser
-我没做任何坏事  -你是他们一伙的
- I didn't do anything  I swear  - You're one of them
不是的 我的意思是 我曾是 但是我逃走了 我也没有杀掉任何人
No  I mean  I was  but I ran away I didn't kill anybody
这到底是谁干的？
Who did this?
他抢了我们的船然后逼我们来这儿
He took over our ship and forced us to come here
-谁 ？ -他的名字叫泰勒
- Who? - His name's Tyler
为什么他要袭击我们？
Why did he attack?
他是个疯子 他想得到永生
He's nuts He thinks he's going to live forever
他要去哪里？你有一秒时间回答
Where did he go? You've got one second
One
等等 我会带你去找到他
Wait  I'll take you to him
-哪儿？-我们达成协议了吗？
- Where?- Do we have a deal?
-修好这艘飞船需要多久？-2小时 最多 我马上就要完工了
- How long to fix this Spacehawk?- Two hours  max  I'm almost there
你把你的扳手丢了 难道你不应该去捡起来吗？
You dropped your wrench Aren't you going to pick it up?
是的
Yeah
我又做了什么吗？
What did I do?
我是个天才
I am a genius
博士 这个最好奏效
Doc  this had better work
我喜欢这种淡淡的柠檬味
I like the hint of lemon
真令人开心
I'm so glad
是的
Yes
然后 我们要去哪儿？
So  where are we going?
他说过他要去一个穿梭泊口
He said he needed to get to a jump port
电脑 设定坐标去最近的宇宙港口
Computer  set co-ordinates for the closest spaceport
那种能容纳C级太空船的
that can handle a class C vessel
搜索 确认 Neo Calcutta 设定航线
Searching  Confirmed Neo Calcutta  Course set
ETA 93 7 个小时
那个 你的名字叫什么
So  what's your name?
禁止说话 禁止乱碰 你最好连呼吸都不要···
Don't talk  don't touch don't even breathe
否则我会杀了 你 明白了吗？-我明白了
or I kill you  Got it?- I got it
请求对接
Request incoming docking co-ordinates
请保持航向
Please continue holding pattern
请停泊到ANUS-6370
Lock in approach at ANUS-6370
-确认 -请表明你的来意
- Confirmed - State the purpose of your visit
-复仇 -处理中
- Revenge - Processing
输入无效 请重新提交
Invalid entry  Resubmit
-处理家事 -确认
- Family business - Confirmed
准许停留48小时
Forty-eight hour access
签证号 URFUKD-881
Visa file number URFUKD-881
请提交身份证明
Please submit identity
FAKK 2行星
FAKK 2
确认 解除对接
Confirmed  Cleared for docking
你喜欢这地方吗？
You like this place?
看上去有很多你的同类
Looks like a lot of your type
在一起待在战斗机4天后 结果还是只得到冷漠对待···
After four days stuck in a Spacehawk getting the cold shoulder
并没有那么糟糕 我们在这里能找到很多乐子
it's not so bad We could have a lot of fun here
你是什么人 可怜虫吗？
What are you  socially deprived?
我不是可怜虫 当然 或许有一点点是
I'm not socially deprived Well  maybe a little
坐下 你在看什么？你在打呼噜
Sit down  What are you looking at?You snore
离我远点 给我闭嘴
Get outta my face  Shut the fuck up '
相比我来的地方这里简直就是天堂
This is heaven compared to where I come from
闭嘴
Shut the fuck up
你确定泰勒在找穿梭泊口？还有他到底要去哪儿？
Are you sure this guy Tyler is lookingfor a jump port? And to where?
我们现在卖的是高级货色 由真正的硅橡胶构成
We're talking high-grade silicone-rubber flesh here
还有PVC骨架 塑料插座能保证满足你的需要
And a PVC skeleton with plastic ball and socket joints for optimum movement
你能为她设定七种发型
You can customise her with a choice of seven synthetic hair dyes
并且还有四档速可以选择
And optional entry ports with four speeds of suction
她很可爱 不是吗？
Loveable  isn't she?
再看看这个
Check this out
她装载了最新的微型传感器架构技术
She's loaded with the latest micro-sensor orgasmatronic technology
还有可扩展的语言库
and an expandable vocabulary
超过200句脏话
of over 200 dirty words
测试结果显示她比真人还要好
Test results indicate she's better than the real thing
来 维纳斯 让大家看看你的本事
Go on  Venus Show the gentleman what you got
请选择性爱模式
Please select your sexual preference
Vaginal  Anal  Oral  Other
只卖2000块
Only 2 000
我不确定 2000块···
I don't know  2 000
当然 或许你更喜欢其他模式
Unless  of course you'd prefer the Fellation Blowfish
病态 扭曲 低级 无耻的混蛋
Sick  twisted  low-life  scum sucking pig
至少我想有人能陪我说会话
At least I'll have someone to talk to
啥？
What?
就是那家伙 那个高个子
That's him  The tall one
-走 -我在这里等着
- Let's go - I'll wait here
但是他会发现我 你根本不知道他的可怕
But he'll see me You don't know what he's like
胆小鬼
Chicken shit
天哪 这真是有趣
God  this is fun
没人能碰这些东西
Nobody touches these
除了我
but me
毛巾
Bar towel
你好 泰勒船长 金属矿产开发商
Hello? Captain Tyler Metal Mammoth Mining
给我们拿点喝的
We need some drinks
我们得抓紧时间 我们可不想错过传送
We should make it fast We don't want to miss the jump
去他的的传送
Screw the jump
我拥有花不完的时间
I've got all the time in the world
除此之外 有意思的事情来了
Besides  something just came up
你刚刚碰到你的白马王子
You just found the man of your dreams
当你杀掉某人时 亲爱的 确保他已经死透了
When you kill someone  darling make sure he's dead
什么情况？
What the hell?
看上去快乐时光结束了
Looks like happy hour is over
-谁来赔这些东西？-这些应该够了
- Who's gonna pay for all of this? - This ought to take care of it
给你 不用找了
Here  Keep the change
什么？可恶
What? Holy shit
炸弹
Grenades
朱莉？
Julie?
你还好吗？
Are you all right?
他死了 但他却死而复生了
He died  And then he was alive again
现在你明白啦
Now you know
我一点也不想知道 他到底是怎么做到的？
I don't know dick  How does he do it?
他注射了一种奇怪的药
He's got this weird potion
那把钥匙会指引他到达永生之所
And a key leading him to the Chamber of lmmortality
为什么你之前不告诉我这些？
Why didn't you tell me that before?
坐下 离我远点 还有给我闭嘴
Sit down  Get outta my face Shut the fuck up
也就是说如果我拿走他的药 他就会死翘翘 是吗？
So if I take away his potion he'll stay dead  right?
如果你做得足够彻底的话
If you can get close enough
那个就是他 是不是？
That's him  isn't it?
可恶 他要离开了
Son of a bitch  he's getting away
宇宙的暴君还需要什么？
What more could the universe want in a tyrant?
完美的身体 完美的大脑
Perfect body  perfect mind
-无法抗拒的魅力 -彻彻底底的神经病
- Irresistible charm - Perfect psycho
神经病？到出来玩游戏的时间了
Psycho? Time to come out and play
想都别想
Don't even think about it
空间跳跃时 总会发生一些事情
The hyperspace jump There's always something
我晚点会弥补你的 甜心
I'll make it up to you later  sweetheart
赶紧让我离开这 你们这群混蛋
Let me out of here  you bastard
科尔斯特号飞船呼叫跳跃中心 设定航线去乌诺布里斯
Cortez to Jump Control Set lock-in for Uroboris
没有历史数据 开始重新设计航线
No pre-set lock-in  Set co-ordinates
特拉肯星系 第9象限 4013区
Quadrant 9  sector 4013 in the Terackian system
扫描地址
Scanning location
警告 没有返程传送泊岸
Warning  No returnjump port
请确认
Please confirm lock-in
确认
Confirmed
我们会一辈子困在那里
It'll take us forever to get back
一旦我们到达那里 这都将不再是问题
That won't be a problem once we get there
我们不可能成功 这就是一条死路
We'll never make it This thing's a death trap
-我们已经走了这么远了 -这点旅程根本不算什么
- It's gotten us this far - This far is nowhere
在超空间航行就是在找死
Spacehawk in hyperspace equals death
收好这个袋子
Stow the bag
-你疯了吗？-我决不能跟丢他
- Are you nuts?- I'm not going to lose him now
你不能尾随他们的跳跃轨道
You can't just piggyback their jump
牵引光速 你疯了吗？我们会被扯碎的···
A tractor beam  Are you insane?We're going to rip to
-那是什么东西？-看来我们来了不速之客
- What the hell is that?- We've got company
啊 不速之客？你什么意思？
Excuse me  company？What do you mean company
看到这个信号了吗？看来有人搭上了我们的跳跃轨道便车
See that blip? It's like somebody hitched onto our jump
这会改变我们的航线 我要他们死 就是现在 宰了他们
That could change our trajectory I want them dead  Now  Take 'em down
但是我从来没有听说过有人能够在超空间进行攻击
But I've never heard of anyone firing on a ship in hyperspace
你还有其他好主意吗？马上照我说的做
Do you have a better idea? Do it  Now
伙计 这是在自杀
Man  that's suicide
-他们完全失去信号了 无人机毁了 -派轰炸机去
- We lost them all  They're toast - Send the bomber
再多说一句话 我就送你去
One more word  and I'll send you
我们被击中了 我就知道
We're hit  I knew it
都怪你
This is all your fault
赶紧做点什么
Do something
通道马上要崩溃了
The tunnel's breaking up
我们不可能成功的
We're not going to make it
好 来吧
Yes  Do it
我感应到那把钥匙就在附近
I sense the key is here
现在 最好由我和齐克先独自弄明白威胁的情况
For the moment  it is best if Zeek and I assess the threat alone
我的药
My ampoules
恐怕要轮到你了
I'm afraid it's down to you
不要 求求你
No  Please
兰伯特 报告损害程度
Lambert  damage report
我要损害程度报告
I want a damage report
别担心 我没事
Don't worry  I'm fine
是么？你以为我关心这个吗？
Yeah? Like I give a shit
现在我们的武器储备还有多少？
What's the status on the double D-40s and munitions?
全部都在
We found a wheel
人员状况？
Personnel?
有78%死亡或失踪
Seventy-eight percent dead or missing
生命迹象扫描呢？
Life-scan?
这里有小镇 好像在北方10-12英里远处
There's a town  looks like it's about 10 or 12 miles north of here
飞行状态？
Flight status?
你是在开玩笑吧
You've got to be kidding
拿起武器 让那些殿后的人···
Gather the weapons what's left of my men
杀掉那些受伤无法战斗的 我们马上出发
shoot the injured  We're moving on
现在还觉得爽吗？
Was it good for you?
从现在开始我要对你这样做
I'll start you off like this
接下来的三四天里 我得依靠你来制造药剂了
The next step  in three or four days depending on your production
你就像一个药物合成储罐一样
will be the body tank
你丫疯子
You're sick
我是个疯狂的天才
I'm a sick genius
我不能呼吸了
I can't breathe
离我远点
Get off my face
你是什么东西？
What are you?
我是齐克 你是谁？
I'm Zeek  what are you?
你的身体真是柔软
You're so soft
我比你想象中的要强 石头人
I'm harder than you think  stone man
你绝对不能碰我的主人奥丁的所有物
Please  you must not touch my master Odin's property
他命我来看守这个
He's left me with the responsibility to guard it
轻松点 我对你看守的东西没兴趣 你的主人在哪里？
Relax  your thing is safe with me Where is your master?
我就是奥丁
I am Odin
请原谅我的小兄弟 他对于自己的职责非常认真
Please excuse my little friend he takes his duties very seriously
-你的名字是？-FAKK 朱莉
- What are you called?- FAKK Julie
朱莉 好柔软 非常柔软
Julie  soft  Very soft
你并不是我们这个世界的人吧？
You're not from our world  are you?
不清楚 这是哪里？
Hardly  What is this place?
乌诺波诺斯 有人称这里家 也有人说这里是地狱
Uroboris  Some call it home Others call it hell
我的主人说你们从天上来
My master says you come from the sky
你手上有那东西吗？你有那把钥匙吗？
Do you have it? Do you have the key?
我不知道什么钥匙？
I don't know anything about a key
我追到这里来是为了杀掉一个疯子 他能够死而复生
I crashed here trying to kill a madman who won't die
我确实看到两个火球
I did see two fireballs
另一个火球坠落到山塔尔城市方向
The other was headed in the direction of a city called Shantaar
离这里不远 我们带你过去
It's not far from here  We'll take you there
嗯嗯 和我们一起走吧
So please  come with us
和我讲讲那个疯子的事情
Tell me more about this madman
他叫泰勒 他将我所有关心的人都杀掉了
Bastard named Tyler killed everyone I ever cared about
我们的传说里提到拥有钥匙的人都会变得疯狂
Our legends say that whoever carries the key  becomes insane
那肯定就是他
That's him all right
我很抱歉 我能感觉到你的悲伤
I'm sorry  I sense your sadness
你的族群只剩下你一个人一定非常难受
It's hard to be the last of your people
没几个像样的 不过总算是个开始
Not much of an army  But it's a start
看 最丑的那个家伙好像坐在我的位子上
Look  The ugliest one seems to be sitting in my chair
喂 最丑的家伙
Hey  you  ugly
你的母亲是下贱的赫克特人
Your mother is a Hectarian whore's handbag
熔岩？我们要跨过这个吗？
Molten lava? We have to cross this?
是的 山塔特 在另一边
Yes  Shantaar lies on the other side
-我讨厌这地方 -我们怎么过去？
- I hate this place - How are we going to cross?
我是查拖格 红河的守护者
I am Chartog  guardian of the Red River
我知道怎么过去
I know the way across
我会告诉你
and I will tell you
你只需要
You just have to
亲我一下
kiss me
没门
No way
怎么呐？宝贝
What's the matter  my precious?
你没发现我的巨大魅力吗？
Don't you find me attractive?
如果这是杀掉泰勒所必须付出的代价的话···
If this is what it takes to kill Tyler
这才像话 帮帮你的朋友
That's a good girl  Help your friends
很快的
It will be over soon
那我返回得亲谁？
Who will I have to kiss to get back?
你在干嘛？
What are you doing?
我们都在等你
We're waiting for you
混蛋 亲这个去吧
Son of a bitch  Kiss this
你们这些人的风俗真奇怪
Your people have strange customs
随你怎么说
Tell me about it
像是死亡呀 永生什么的
Mortality sucks  immortality sucks
所有这些鬼东西
Everything sucks
哦 见鬼
Oh  shit
这真是搓
This really sucks
那家伙是你寻找的人吗？
Is he the one you search for?
哦 是的
Oh  yeah
哈 上呀 泰勒
Yeah  Come on  Tyler
我是你的新头头 是我
I'm your new leader  Me
现在我们惨了
Now we're up the creek
当你杀掉某人时
When you kill someone
确保他已经死透了
make sure they're dead
哟 宝贝
Yo  baby
我是泰勒 你的新主人
I am Tyler  Your new lord
盲目的欢呼声真令人陶醉
Blind adulation makes me so horny
给我个女人
Bring me a wench
主人 他就是那个持有钥匙的人 不是吗？
Master  he's the one with the key  isn't he?
恐怕就凭我们的力量对付不了他
He's far too powerful for us to deal with alone
让我来
Leave that to me
朱莉 你太冲动了 三思而行呐
Julie  you are too impulsive Please  think about this
-考虑什么东西？-那把钥匙
- Think about what?- The key
-你不明白 -你担心的是那把钥匙
- You don't understand - You worry about the key
泰勒是我的
Tyler's mine
她心里只剩下对复仇的渴望
She is letting her thirst for revenge rule her mind
一个新造型 但是··
A little retro  but hey
他们在哪里发现你的？
Where'd they find you?
我听说你很特别 所以不辞万里来见你
I hear you're very special I've come a long way to meet you
-你不是机器人吧？-为什么你不自己来试试？
- You're not a robot  are you?- Why don't you find out for yourself?
我想我死了 并且去了天堂
I could say I've died and gone to heaven  but
那不可能
that wouldn't be true
哪部分？死掉抑或是去天堂？
Which part  the dying or the heaven?
你
You
我知道我的魅力无人可挡 你到底想要什么呢？
I know I'm irresistible but what do you want?
我要你
I want you
还有你拥有的一切
and what you have
我拥有获得永生的钥匙
There's a price to pay for immortality
宇宙也即将付出迎来变革
and the universe is going to pick up the tab
多么具有独创性
How original
每个国王都必须有一个皇后
Every king must have a queen
你想要我？
Do you want me?
你不妨大胆猜一猜
Take a wild guess
永远？
Forever?
闭嘴
Shut up
这次不行
Not this time
贱人
Bitch
去死吧
Time to die
死吧
Die
你在做什么？
What are you doing?
-停下 -我做不到 这是主人命令
- Stop - I can't  The master told me
你这个蠢石头
You stupid rock
我怎么可能会死在这里？
What does it take to get laid around here?
我抓到他了 就在刚才 我明明马上就能杀掉他的
I had him  Ten more seconds and he was dead
我们认为你陷入困境了
We thought you were in trouble
朱莉 太晚了
Julie  it's too late
这已经不再仅仅是你和泰勒之间的事情了
It's not just about you and Tyler
泰勒寻找的东西就藏在圣域
What Tyler seeks lies within the walls of the Holylands
他会到来并审判我们
He will come and we will all be judged
你说你没找到他们是什么意思？
What do you mean you can't find them?
你居然会跟丢一个6尺女人和一块会说话的石头？
How do you lose a 6-foot bitch with a talking rock?
你们是干嘛吃的？
How do you do that?
-我们到处都找遍了  -你们这帮蠢货
- We looked everywhere - You idiots
集合部队
Gather the troops
这就是？
This is it?
我相信得用点酒水和社会交际技巧来融入你们
I sure could use a drink and a little social give and take
主意不错
There goes that idea
能不能休息一会？我年纪有点大了
Can we stop for a moment?I'm not as young as I once was
我来查看周围的状况
I'll see what lies beyond
伊甸很美丽
Eden was beautiful
可是被他毁掉了
Then he destroyed it
主人 你过来看看
Master  come see
是时候进行下一阶段了
It's time for the next phase
求求你
Please
五分钟内 你将失去所有感觉
In five minutes  you will lose all senses
你就好像安静地死去了一样
It will seem like a very peaceful dying
什么？我们来了不速之客
What? We have company
你喜欢这样吗？
Do you like this?
你不应该那样做的
You shouldn't have done that
现在我很伤心
Now I'm really upset
我很担心 主人  朱莉进去有好一会了
I am worried  Master The soft one has been inside too long
这儿 小家伙
Here  kitty
我知道你在哪儿
I know where you are
我能闻到你
I can smell you
救命
Help me
-凯瑞 其他人呢？-他们都死了
- Kerrie  what about the others?- They're all dead
抓住我
Hang on to me
没事
It's okay
就在这附近
Nearly there
快跑
Hurry  run
那不是我们坠毁的地方吗？
Isn't that where we crashed?
我的药剂
My ampoules
我会带上这把斧头然后找到那个贱人
I've had it up to here with that bitch
当我找到她 我会让她不朽 这样我就可以不断折磨她 杀死她
When I find her  I'll make her immortal so I can screw her and kill her
每天 每个小时 来娱乐自己
every hour of every day for all eternity
我们现在向圣域前进
We march on the Holyland now
钥匙所到之处 恐惧如影随形
Where the key goes  horror follows
一切都将臣服于永生之下
All in the sacred name of immortality
为什么是我们？
Why us?
难道你们那本古书没教你们关于阿肯人的事情？
Do your ancient books not teach you about the Arakacians?
我们没有古书
We have no ancient books
阿肯人被毁灭了 因此我们才能生活在和平中
They were destroyed so our people could live in peace
同时也失去了关于过去那些邪恶之事的记忆
without the memory of past evil
忘记历史只会令邪恶东山再起 朱莉
To forget history is to allow evil to rise again  Julie
然后到来更多的罪恶和混乱
More sinister and ruthless than ever
-泰勒是阿肯人吗？    -他不是
- Is Tyler an Arakacian?- He is not
很多实际以前 阿肯人发现了古神之泪
Many centuries ago  the Arakacians discovered an ancient tear
在宇宙形成过程中所产生的所有造物之中
in the fabric of the universe from which flowed a liquid
它能够赐予永生
capable of bestowing immortality
他们奴役我的祖先强迫他们制造一个密室
They enslaved my ancestors and forced them to build a chamber
密室就在应许之地用来收藏那古神之泪
in the Holylands to contain this unnatural power
因此阿肯人才能实行残暴地统治 直到
And so it was that the Arakacians ruled in infamy until
我的祖先锁住密室并将钥匙流放到宇宙深处
my people were able to lock the chamber and cast the key deep into space
没有赐予永生的古神之泪 阿肯人变得普通
Without their life-giving waters the Arakacians became mortal
我们最终打败他们
and we were finally able to defeat them
但是现在泰勒拥有钥匙
But now Tyler has the key
是的 那把钥匙能够带来永生的可能
Yes  The key which holds the promise of immortality
但是也会令他发疯
but also renders its bearer insane
就像诅咒一样
Such is the curse
可能永生？但他已经不可战胜了
The promise of immortality?He's already invincible
不 他还不是
No  He is not
那把钥匙将会指引他找到古神之泪
The key is guiding him to the everlasting waters
但是他还没有得到它
but he has yet to reach them
为什么他要摧毁伊甸？
Why did he have to destroy Eden?
阿肯人也曾经占领你们故乡
The Arakacians also occupied your colony
如同他们蹂躏宇宙其他地方时一样 他们在伊甸储藏了一些古神之泪
and stored some of the liquid there as they ravaged the universe
这么多年过去 古神之泪遍布伊甸
Over time it seeped into the earth
你的族人逐渐将它吸入自己的身体中
Your people absorbed traces of it into their systems
泰勒便从他们的身体中提取药剂
Which Tyler distilled from their bodies
但这并不以令他不朽
Not enough to render him immortal
可也足够他得到力量到达密室
but now he has the strength to reach the chamber
就因为他对力量的渴望便毁灭了我的族群
A whole people destroyed because of the lust for power of one man
这种事在以前也发生过 朱莉 并且以后也会重演
It has happened before  Julie It will happen again
但绝不会是泰勒
Not with Tyler
欢迎回来 奥丁长老
Welcome back  Master Odin
-奥丁 那把钥匙是不是已经来到这里了？-恐怕是的
- Odin  the key? ls it here?- I'm afraid so
如同我们所说 运输队伍
As we speak  the carrier
还有山塔特的渣滓们正在向我们的城市而来
and the vile scum of Shantaar descend upon our city
我们必须尽我们所能做好准备 我们要战斗直到死亡
We have done all we can to prepare We will fight to the death
你们认识？
You know each other?
他在学校时打算救我
He tried to save me at the school
那没什么
It was nothing
你们在哪里认识的？
And where did you meet?
我们是姐妹
We're sisters
姐妹？
Sisters
长老都被杀掉了 我们中一定有叛徒
The elders have been killed There's a traitor among us
警告其他人
Warn the others
就在这里
There it is
永生的密室 里面就是古神之泪
The Chamber of lmmortality that holds the everlasting waters
最后一个
The last one
大家准备战斗 上
Everybody fight  Come on
越来越糟了
This is going to suck
傻瓜
You fool
那是我最后一个了
That was my last one
-谢谢你 软家伙   -不用谢
- Thank you  soft one - Anytime
喂 混蛋
Hey  asshole
又是你
You again
你想我了吗？
Did you miss me?
你总是伤害你爱的人
You always hurt the ones you love
像这样吗？
Like this?
保持这样子 我马上回来
Hold that pose  I'll be right back
这是我的 全都是我的
It's mine  It's all mine
来吧 贱人 你真的惹火我了
Bring it on  bitch You're really starting to piss me off
你没资格拿到圣水
You are not worthy of the Holy Waters
至少今天不行
Not today
记住今天是你的忌日
Remember this on your way to hell
FAKK 2
这疯狂的事情马上就要结束了
The insanity has to end now
我们必须毁掉那把钥匙
We must destroy the key
或者不用
Perhaps not
为什么？
Why?
因为我是阿肯人
Because I am Arakacian
我的演技骗过了那些令人恶心的圣域人
My charade fooled the insufferable Holylanders
还有那个愚蠢的石头
And even that little stone idiot
你难道真的认为一个普通人能够阻止我？
What makes you think a pathetic mortal could stop me?
你个蠢货
You fools
我必须完成我的使命
I must fulfil my destiny
-你应该如此  -齐克 我命令你
- You must - Zeek  I command you
再见 软家伙 我永远不会忘记你
Good-bye  soft one  I'll never forget you
结束了
It's over
-让我来帮你    -哦 不会吧 他还活着
- Let me help you - Oh  no  He survived
你还好吗？
Are you okay?
你看我怎么样 你这个白痴？
What does it look like  you dickhead?
永恒意味着长久的孤独
Eternity is a long time to spend alone
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
这是不是意味着我们要变得不朽？
Does this mean we're all going to be immortal?
因为如果这是真的 你知道···
'Cause if that's true  you know
听我说 我要去四处转转很长一段时间
Listen  I'm going to be around for a long time
谁拿着钥匙？
Who took the key?
这是不是意味着我们现在是朋友？
Does this mean we're friends now?
因为我给你添了不少麻烦 所以···
'Cause I've been putting up with a lot of your crap  so
我认为现在是回报的时间了 来吧 你知道你是爱我的
l think it's payback time Come on  you know you love me
就这样 那把通往永生密室的钥匙
And so the key to the chamber of immortality
再次被流放到宇宙沉寂的深处
was once again cast out into the silent gulfs of space
一个新的石像守护者看守着它对抗邪恶
with a new stone protector to guard it against evil